Email: maaz.javed07@gmail.com

Date of Birth: 31st July 1997

Phone: +923223302046

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/maaz-javed-mj07

Results driven professional with a track record of optimizing processes and driving efficiency. Cultivating and expanding client relationships to drive revenue growth. Expert in strategic account management and grabbing new business, consistently delivering tailored solutions to meet client needs and exceed expectations.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Business Operations Executive & Client Success Manager**

May 2022 – Jan 2024

#### Invozone Pvt. Ltd - Lahore

- Researched on clients and their products to understand their vision/goals to offer a personalized experience.
- Managed and oversee the complete sales lifecycle throughout the customer journey.
- Worked with C-suite to make project-related strategic decisions by making sure client's preferences and goals are prioritized.
- Used different marketing and sales strategies to bring in the new leads and exceeding targets.
- Developed and cultivated lucrative relationship to boost long term business success and increase profit levels.
- Possess experience working with clients across various industries and countries, including the USA, Canada, UK, Gulf and European countries.
- Identified opportunities for upsell and cross sell to existing clients and bring in the new business through different platforms.
- Monitored client satisfaction levels regularly, identifying pain points and opportunities for improvement.
- Strong analytical, problem-solving, and critical thinking skills along with ability to work on time sensitive tasks.

### **Customer Insights Executive**

Nov 2021- Apr 2022

### Skyelectric Pvt. Ltd - Lahore

- Conduct daily operations and sales functions to maximize revenue, customer satisfaction and organizational productivity.
- Data analysis to improve and optimize performance, capture meaningful insights, and turn them into business benefits.
- Use statistical and predictive techniques to identify gaps to make customer experience better.
- Building and maintaining profitable relationships with
- Validating closed sales and raising red flags where correction is needed to ensure seamless customer experience as well as to improve brand image.
- Handled complaints, provided appropriate solutions and alternatives within appropriate timeframe and followed up to achieve resolution.

## **Resident Engineer**

Oct 2019 - Oct 2021

#### Multinet Pakistan Pvt. Ltd - Lahore

- Voice of the customer for all the issues related to stakeholder services.
- Resolve all customer queries within required timeframe and provide assistance and monitor all proactive activities and new deployments.
- Evaluate all improvement operations and ensure availability of all resources. Prepare outage schedules and provide recommendation for restoration work.
- Manage and maintain accurate field notes. Prepare comprehensive assessment, SLA reports and maintain flow of technical information.
- Responded to technical concerns quickly and effectively devised solutions.
- Built vast technical knowledge and proficiency in troubleshooting.
- Advised senior personnel on potential process improvements to increase support quality and expedite ticket fulfillment.
- Performed root cause analysis of reported issues to decisively discern and enact corrections.

### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelors in Electrical Engineering** (Telecommunication)

NED University of Engineering & Technology (2019) -Karachi

# **SKILLS**

Project Management, Customer Relationship Management, Business Development, Process Improvement, Product and Service Sales, Troubleshooting & Diagnostics.

### **TOOLS**

